freeje.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy

Freeje Privacy Policy

BETA COMPANY  sp.z o.o. ("Freeje" or "we" or "us" or "our" or other similar pronouns) takes your privacy matters very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how we receive, collect and use information in connection with our website located at Freeje.com (the "Site"), the Freeje software ("Freeje App"), and other products and services provided on the [http://freeje.com](http://freeje.com/) website (all of the foregoing, collectively, the "Service").

By visiting this Site or using the Service, you are accepting the policies and practices described in this Policy, as such Policy may be amended from time to time. Each time you visit the Site or use the Service, you agree and expressly consent to our collection, use and disclosure of the information that you provide as described in this Policy.

To be clear about the terminology we are using, when we use the phrase "Personal Information" in this Policy, we mean information about you that is personally identifiable, like your name, address, e-mail address, billing information, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with this personal information. When we use the phrase "Anonymous Information" in this Policy, we mean information that is not personally identifiable, or linked to your Personal Information such as aggregated information, general demographic information and IP addresses. Anonymous Information does not necessarily enable identification of individual persons.

1\. Collection and Use of Information

Freeje App

When you install the Freeje App or register on the Site, you will be asked to provide us with your phone number and email to allow us access to your mobile device's address book.

A copy of the phone numbers and names in your address book (but not emails, notes or any other Personal Information in your address book) will be stored on our servers and will only be used to:

(a) notify you when your contacts become available on Freeje,

(b) indicate which of your contacts is already a Freeje user,

(c) correctly display the name of each contact as it appears in your address book when a call is received.

(d) sync your contacts with Freeje running on Android tablets and phones and iOS devices.

The copy of your address book (names and phones) may be stored on a live database. This database does not have a "historical backup". If you delete the address book from our servers (more about this below), it will be deleted instantly and permanently.

Your phone number will be used for identification purposes as one of your Freeje user ID. Email will be the another user ID.

Since Freeje users may add your Freeje number to their address book and see that you registered to Freeje, we do not consider the fact that your Freeje number exists on Freeje as private information.

Freeje also maintains a Call Detail Record (CDR - see [http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Call_detail_record](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/call_detail_record)) for each call that goes through the system. These are industry standard records used by all phone companies. We maintain this information in order to better understand network behavior and trends (numbers of calls made by users, typical destinations, call lengths, network type, etc.), detect potential outages and technical issues (this helps us notice things like a drop in call volume in a certain geography, a shift in call length, a change in typical networks, etc.) and for public safety reasons. All log analysis is done in an anonymous, aggregate, non-personally identifiable manner. 

Freeje may interact with your phone's SMS inbox or call history for the sole purpose of service activation, placing incoming messages in your inbox, reading the contents of the activation SMS sent to you by Freeje. WE WILL NOT ACCESS THE CONTENTS OF ANY OTHER SMS.

Cookies and Other Automatically Collected Data

If you have permitted your computer to accept cookies, we may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at the Site. Cookies may be used to analyze the Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. A cookie may enable us to relate your use of our Site to other information about you, including your Personal Information. All of these purposes serve to improve and personalize your experience on our Site. Most Web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. Additionally, if you have a Flash player installed on your computer, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Site or certain areas or features of the Site.

Our servers may automatically collect data about your Internet address when you visit the Site. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you are on the Internet. When you request pages from our Site, our servers may log your IP Address and, if applicable, your domain name. Your IP Address is used to help identify you and to gather demographic information about our members and users as a whole, but does not include personally identifiable information. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another web site or a search engine); the pages you visit on this Site; the web site you visit after this Site; the ads you see and/or click on; other information about the type of Web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Site or a referral site; and other Web usage activity and data logged by our servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our Service. Such information may also be used to gather demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider.

We will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of our users.

Any or all of these activities with regard to Site usage information may be performed on our behalf by our service providers, including, for example, our analytics vendor(s) and our e-mail management partner(s).

Third-Party Sites and Privacy Practices

You may arrive at our Site and/or download the Freeje App from another website. In addition, our Site may contain links that will let you leave our Site and access another website. Websites linked to or from our Site are not under the control of Freeje and it is possible that these websites have a different privacy policy. Our Policy applies solely to Personal Information that is acquired on the Site or through your use of our Service, and/or your relationship with Freeje. We urge you to be careful when you enter any Personal Information online. We accept no responsibility or liability for these other websites.

Analytics Collection

Freeje uses Google Analytics to help us anonymously track and report user/visitor behavior information and users' standard log information to the Site and the Freeje App. This information (including but not limited to: IP address, data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and information processing) helps us analyze and evaluate how the Freeje App and Site are used as part of our ongoing efforts to improve the Site and Freeje App's features and services. No personally identifying data is included in this type of reporting. Google Analytics may have access to your information only for the purposes of performing these tasks and on behalf of Freeje and under obligation similar in those in this Privacy Policy. For more information about the terms that govern Google Analytics, please visit the [Google Analytics terms of service](http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/tos.html). 

2\. Sharing and Disclosure of Information

We do not rent, sell, or share any information about our users with any third-parties, except as specifically described herein. We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe such action is necessary to:

(a) comply with the law, or legal process served on us;

(b) protect and defend our rights or property (including the enforcement of our agreements); or

(c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of our Service or members of the public.

In order to provide you with Freeje products you have requested, Freeje may sometimes, if necessary, share your Personal Information (excluding your address book and related information) and traffic data with trusted partner service providers and/or agents, for example: banking organizations or other providers of payment and analytical services, customer support, or hosting services. Freeje will always require these third parties to take appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect your personal data and traffic data and to observe the relevant legislation. Freeje will never share your address book information with any third party, except as may be required by law (see below).

The following is a description of how we may share your Personal Information with trusted third party partners. Should we add additional partners, we will immediately update this description:

1\. We use third party companies in order to send you an authentication SMS when you register with Freeje. In order to send you the SMS, we send one of these third party companies your phone number and the authentication message. These third parties are contractually obligated to only use your phone number for the transmission of the authentication SMS.

2\. If we fail to send you an SMS (this happens in certain cases) you may ask us to call you and verify phone number. This is done using a third party automated phone system. In order to call you, we provide this third party partner with your phone number and send the "audio content" of the call to them. The third party partner in turn will typically use another phone provider who may use another phone provider and so on until the call reaches you. This is an industry standard mechanism for the transmission of phone calls. The third party partner is contractually obligated to only use your phone number for the completion of the authentication phone call.

3\. We may use Push Notification Services to notify you about various events related to the app. If we do, the phone number or the name of the person calling you or sending you a message may be part of the notification. This message is sent to the push notification service provider, for delivery to your device.

4\. We use third parties to process the payment and/or billing information that you submit on our Site or through the Freeje App to facilitate payment transactions. We require that these third parties take the appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect your personal data and traffic data and to comply with relevant laws, but we are not liable or responsible for these third party transactions. Therefore, you should review such third party terms and conditions before providing your payment or billing information.

We may disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance that disclosure of information is necessary.

We may from time to time ask you to provide information about your experiences, which will be used to measure and improve quality. You are at no time under any obligation to provide any of such data. Any and all information which is voluntarily submitted in feedback forms on the Site or any survey that you accept to take part in is used for the purposes of reviewing this feedback and improving the Freeje software, products and websites.

We may contact you to send you messages about faults and service issues. Furthermore, we reserve the right to use email, the Freeje software or SMS to notify you of any eventual claims related to your use of our software, websites and/or products, including without limitation claims of violation of third party rights.

3\. Children's Privacy

Freeje websites and software clients are not intended for or designed to attract anyone under the age of 13 and we do not intentionally or knowingly collect Personal Information on our sites from anyone under the age of 13 (or older in some jurisdictions). We encourage parents to be involved in the online activities of their children to ensure that no information is collected from a child without parental permission.

4\. Security

We take reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although we cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, we have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in place to protect Personal Information. Personal Information is stored on our servers and protected by secured networks to which access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.

5\. Business Transitions

In the event that we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. As part of such a transaction the new entity will be required to commit to the same level of protection of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we cannot obtain such a commitment, we will not perform the business transition.

We will post a notice on this Site of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information we may have prior to such transfer.

6\. Changes to Policy

From time to time, we may revise this Policy. We reserve the right to update or modify this Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time with or without notice. However, we will not use your Personal Information in a way that is materially different than the uses described in this Policy without giving you an opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. We will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information we collect, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. You agree to review the Policy periodically so that you are aware of any modifications. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to any changes and signifies your agreement to the terms of our Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, you should not use the Site, the Freeje App, or any other Service.

7\. Change Information

If you provided your e-mail address to us and wish to update it, you may do so by sending an e-mail to  [info@freeje.com](mailto:info@freeje.com).

If you no longer wish to receive e-mail communication from us, such as offers, updates and newsletters, you may opt-out of receiving such communications by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication. 

8\. Contact Information

Please direct all questions in connection with this Policy via e-mail to  [info@freeje.com](mailto:info@freeje.com) or via call to +48 22 2062180
